[{"answer": "It's looking pretty good that she'll be in a position where she can make the decision to run for her seat again.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 15, "question": "Will Gabby run again?", "qSentId": 14}, {"answer": "Well, it was -- for us, it was typical.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 33, "question": "How did it start for you?", "qSentId": 32}, {"answer": "Well, it's interesting.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 43, "question": "Could anything prepare you for that call?", "qSentId": 42}, {"answer": "Yes, so I wasn't even sure -- after I got off the phone with Pia, it was a very short conversation.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 51, "question": "And you ring back to get more information, didn't you?", "qSentId": 50}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 64, "question": "Were you hearing the same kind of erroneous information?", "qSentId": 63}, {"answer": "Well, I --", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "How did you find out that she was still alive?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "So the airplane also had a phone.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 89, "question": "For a fact?", "qSentId": 88}, {"answer": "Well, it was a busy day.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 95, "question": "What is the first thing that you find there when you get there?", "qSentId": 94}, {"answer": "I was pretty focused on what was going on with her.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 124, "question": "Were you getting any sense of how this was playing out around the world, or were you very much locked in that room now?", "qSentId": 123}, {"answer": "So, yes, part of me feared that.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 148, "question": "When you saw her like that, if you're honest, looking back on it, did you fear then, you were never going to get your wife back in any kind of normal form?", "qSentId": 147}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "Isn't it?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "Well, about 10 minutes after he walked out of the room, Kirsten Gillibrand and Debbie Wasserman Schultz, two of her very good friends from Congress, were there in the room with us, and they were talking to Gabby, you know, for a good amount of time.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 189, "question": "Do you remember much of that time, or is that all just a blur to you?", "qSentId": 188}, {"answer": "Even before she opened her eyes, she would -- you know, with her eyes closed, she took -- I took my ring off my finger once.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 205, "question": "And with Gabby, what was the moment for you when you thought for the first time, I may get my wife back?", "qSentId": 204}, {"answer": "As she used to do, just like I'm doing here, and she would, you know, just -- you know very naturally, you know -- so you knew she was in there.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 209, "question": "As she used to do?", "qSentId": 208}, {"answer": "Well, it was reported that she said the word \"toast,\" which she did around that day.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "What was the first word that she spoke?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "I did -- yes, I was standing right there.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "Were you there when she first said that?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "Well, it feels great.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 231, "question": "How does that feel?", "qSentId": 230}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 241, "question": "But are you going to get through it?", "qSentId": 240}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 245, "question": "You can get through it?", "qSentId": 244}, {"answer": "Well, you know, a lot of people have rehab that affects one part of their body, the relearning how to walk or relearning how to use their limbs or in her case, you know, the -- the speech.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 251, "question": "And it was tough, hard, every tiny step of the way, right?", "qSentId": 250}, {"answer": "It's amazing.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 265, "question": "Isn't that amazing?", "qSentId": 264}, {"answer": "I didn't know any of it.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 268, "question": "Did you know any of this before?", "qSentId": 267}, {"answer": "Well, things she knew well.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "Were there particular songs or singers that seemed to have a particular effect?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "Yes, yes.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 285, "question": "So Don McLean has basically got a lot to be thanked for, right?", "qSentId": 284}, {"answer": "So Megan Morrow, the music therapist, would play some U2 and some -- I mean stuff that she's familiar with and likes to hear.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 298, "question": "It hurts you, right?", "qSentId": 297}, {"answer": "Well, we had a plan that we would tell her things as she asked.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "How did she react in the moment when you were able to finally tell her?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "Well, initially, she -- you know, she was -- she was shocked.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 320, "question": "And how was she able to react to it?", "qSentId": 319}, {"answer": "Looking forward to coming home.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 330, "question": "BONO, U2 VOCALIST: What's on your mind?", "qSentId": 329}, {"answer": "Well, I met her about seven years ago on a trip to China, with a group of young, Young Leaders Forum.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 356, "question": "When did you first meet Gabby?", "qSentId": 355}, {"answer": "Yes, I remember seeing her for the first time.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 362, "question": "Do you remember the first moment?", "qSentId": 361}, {"answer": "Well, we didn't go on a date until -- I went -- after that trip, I went over a year without seeing her.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 366, "question": "And when did you realize this was actually potentially the woman you wanted to spend the rest of your life with?", "qSentId": 365}, {"answer": "Yes, a maximum security prison.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "Of all the hot dates, huh?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "Well, she laughs at my jokes.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 374, "question": "What was it about her that you liked so much?", "qSentId": 373}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "There must be moments in your relationship early on when you say -- honestly, I would love to have dinner next Wednesday, but I'm actually going to be in space?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 410, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 409}, {"answer": "Well, we don't know.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 415, "question": "Has it affected her ability to have a child?", "qSentId": 414}, {"answer": "It would be.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "It would be an incredible way to seal the recovery, wouldn't it?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "She's doing great.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "How is she right now?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "Well, that Gabby is alive, first of all.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 438, "question": "What would you be thanking, in particular?", "qSentId": 437}, {"answer": "It was.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "Really special moment, that, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "I would say neither.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "What is the reality?", "qSentId": 504}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 523, "question": "Have any of his family made any attempt to contact you?", "qSentId": 522}, {"answer": "You know, I'm -- you know, I don't spend a lot of time thinking about it.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "Are you surprised at that?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "ELLY: As a family?", "qSentId": 530}, {"answer": "Well, you know, she doesn't spend a lot of time being angry about it.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "Does Gabby have any thoughts towards the man that shot her?", "qSentId": 537}, {"answer": "I'd say it is now.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 558, "question": "Is that a fair reflection of how she is now in terms of being able to talk and so on?", "qSentId": 557}, {"answer": "So I don't know.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 564, "question": "What's your gut instinct?", "qSentId": 563}, {"answer": "I don't think so.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 576, "question": "Have her politics changed?", "qSentId": 575}, {"answer": "You know, we haven't talked a lot about it.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 582, "question": "Has her view of gun control changed at all?", "qSentId": 581}, {"answer": "Well, certainly, you know, in her case, with one event having such a serious impact on her health, I think she'd remind people to be thankful, you know, for your health and for your family and, you know, for being alive.", "docId": "111123pmt", "aSentId": 613, "question": "What do you think if Gabby was here she would say to people that they should be thankful for, given this life-changing thing she's been through?", "qSentId": 612}]